<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Tag in Pune, Maharashtra, India &#8211; Expert Zone</title>
	<atom:link href="https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/tags/tag/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity</link>
	<description>Just another site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 06:10:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/cropped-download-1-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>Tag in Pune, Maharashtra, India &#8211; Expert Zone</title>
	<link>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>National Constitution Center</title>
		<link>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/national-constitution-center/</link>
					<comments>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/national-constitution-center/#reviews</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 06:10:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/national-constitution-center/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Experience It only four pages long, but the U.S. Constitution is among the most influential and important documents in the history of the world. The 160,000-square-foot National Constitution Center explores and explains this amazing document through high-tech exhibits, artifacts, and interactive displays. The Kimmel Theater, a 350-seat star-shaped theater, features Freedom Rising, a multimedia<a class="moretag" href="https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/national-constitution-center/"> Read more...</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3>The Experience</h3>
<p>	It only four pages long, but the U.S. Constitution is among the most influential and important documents in the history of the world.</p>
<p>	The 160,000-square-foot National Constitution Center explores and explains this amazing document through high-tech exhibits, artifacts, and interactive displays. The Kimmel Theater, a 350-seat star-shaped theater, features Freedom Rising, a multimedia production combining film, a live actor and video projection on a 360° screen to tell the stirring story of We the people.</p>
<p>	Then experience it yourself: don judicial robes to render your opinion on key Supreme Court cases, then take the Presidential oath of the office.</p>
<p>	In Signers Hall, where life-size bronze figures of the Constitution&acute;s signers and dissenters are displayed, visitors can choose to sign or dissent.</p>
<p>	One of the rare original public copies of the Constitution is on display.</p>
<h3>History </h3>
<p>	Freedom of speech, protection from unlawful search and seizure, and other individual rights were not part of the original Constitution. Recognizing its imperfections, the authors built in a mechanism to amend the Constitution, making it adaptable for unknown eventualities.</p>
<p>	The first ten amendments guaranteeing numerous personal freedoms &#8211; The Bill of Rights &#8211; were not ratified until 1791.</p>
<h3>Insider Tip </h3>
<p>	While the Center hosts amazing evergreen presentations, take a look at the Events Calendar for the latest premiere or traveling exhibit.</p>
<h3>Kids Stuff </h3>
<p>	The Center frequently hosts special events with a focus on children that include informative and engaging hands-on activities. For specific information, check out the Center website.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/national-constitution-center/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
