<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Food Nightlife in Pune, Maharashtra, India &#8211; Expert Zone</title>
	<atom:link href="https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/category/food-nightlife/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity</link>
	<description>Just another site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 06:18:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/cropped-download-1-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>Food Nightlife in Pune, Maharashtra, India &#8211; Expert Zone</title>
	<link>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Morimoto</title>
		<link>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/morimoto/</link>
					<comments>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/morimoto/#reviews</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 06:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/morimoto/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Stephen Starr creative Japanese restaurant has garnered all kinds of national and international attention since opening a few years back. Located a block from Independence Hall on Chestnut Street, Morimoto has an interior &#8211; awash in glass and colors &#8211; that is both striking and serene in its design. The restaurant&#180;s namesake and head chef,<a class="moretag" href="https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/morimoto/"> Read more...</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>	Stephen Starr creative Japanese restaurant has garnered all kinds of national and international attention since opening a few years back. Located a block from Independence Hall on Chestnut Street, Morimoto has an interior &#8211; awash in glass and colors &#8211; that is both striking and serene in its design.</p>
<p>	The restaurant&acute;s namesake and head chef, Morimoto (of Food Network&acute;s Iron Chef fame), has created a menu offering the very best in contemporary Japanese cusine. While regulars flock here for the exquisitely prepared sushi, Morimoto offers diners a broad spectrum of flavors that delve beyond nigiri and sashimi.</p>
<p>	In recent years, the restaurant has made it onto Gourmet magazine&acute;s “Best Restaurants in America” list and Conde Nast Traveler magazine 50 Hot Tables in America. Today Morimoto remains one of the hottest spots to dine in Center City and continues to receive rave reviews from regulars and first-timers alike.</p>
<p>	That said, be sure to call ahead for reservations.</p>
<h3>Insider Tip </h3>
<p>	The mezzanine level lounge is a great spot to have a pre-meal cocktail while waiting for your table. You can enjoy a sake or try a “Sakura” &#8211; a cosmo made with Sake &#8211; in the sleek space that overlooks the brilliant restaurant below.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/morimoto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sampan</title>
		<link>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/sampan/</link>
					<comments>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/sampan/#reviews</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 06:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/sampan/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Chef and charismatic television star Michael Schulson returns to Philadelphia with the opening of Sampan, a modern Asian restaurant where he serves the acclaimed cuisine that has made him one of the country&#180;s highly sought-after culinary talents. Schulson returns to Philadelphia after having opened Buddakan in New York City for Stephen Starr and Izakaya at<a class="moretag" href="https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/sampan/"> Read more...</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>	Chef and charismatic television star Michael Schulson returns to Philadelphia with the opening of Sampan, a modern Asian restaurant where he serves the acclaimed cuisine that has made him one of the country&acute;s highly sought-after culinary talents.</p>
<p>	Schulson returns to Philadelphia after having opened Buddakan in New York City for Stephen Starr and Izakaya at the Borgata in Atlantic City and then having gone on to star in Style network&acute;s popular series Pantry Raid and TLC Ultimate Cake Off.</p>
<p>	Chef Schulson has been looking forward to a time when he could come back to Philadelphia and cook in a small, personal space, which he has now achieved with Sampan. To him, Sampan is a place where he can prepare serious food from across Asia while interacting with guests and sharing his love of the cuisine with them.</p>
<h3>Design </h3>
<p>	Designed by Philadelphia&acute;s Sparks Design, Sampan features distressed metals, reclaimed timber and a rustic, natural aesthetic anchored by a custom-crafted, color washed painting that lends a warm ambiance to the space. In contrast to the large scale restaurants such as Manhattan&acute;s Buddakan and West Philadelphia&acute;s Pod, where Chef Schulson served as executive chef, this 80-seat gem is a cozy setting that allows his passion for Asian flavors, thoughtfully prepared, to shine.</p>
<h3>Cuisine </h3>
<p>	Schulson&acute;s says his mission at Sampan is to make the more exotic and unfamiliar flavors of Asian cuisine accessible and inviting to American palates.</p>
<p>	Sampan menu is composed of a variety of small plates &#8211; Chef Schulson&acute;s preferred way to cook because it is ideal for sampling and sharing. Tempting dishes include: his signature Edamame Dumplings, with truffles, shoots and sake broth; Thai Chicken Wings with pickles, mint and basil; Pekin Duck with tamarind pancakes, scallions and cucumbers; Lamb Satay with yakitori, penko and ginger; Crispy Chili Crab with Hong Kong noodles, black beans and ginger chips; Mao Pao Tofu with pork, ginger and garlic; and Wild Mushroom Salad with goat cheese, puffed rice and truffles.</p>
<p>	Prices range from $5 to $19.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/sampan/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Rittenhouse</title>
		<link>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/the-rittenhouse/</link>
					<comments>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/the-rittenhouse/#reviews</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 06:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/the-rittenhouse/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A deluxe hotel like The Rittenhouse deserves a deluxe restaurant, a fitting description for Lacroix, named “Restaurant of the Year” in 2003 by Esquire magazine. Located on the second floor of the Rittenhouse Hotel, Lacroix features elegant décor and a broad view of Rittenhouse Square, which combine to make the ambiance at Lacroix as enjoyable<a class="moretag" href="https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/the-rittenhouse/"> Read more...</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>	A deluxe hotel like The Rittenhouse deserves a deluxe restaurant, a fitting description for Lacroix, named “Restaurant of the Year” in 2003 by Esquire magazine.</p>
<p>	Located on the second floor of the Rittenhouse Hotel, Lacroix features elegant décor and a broad view of Rittenhouse Square, which combine to make the ambiance at Lacroix as enjoyable as the meal itself.</p>
<p>	The creative French menu changes with the season and in the past has included favorites like pumpkin soup with fried shallots and tuna steak with salmis sauce. The wine list is excellent and extensive &#8211; thanks to the 4,000-bottle wine cellar .</p>
<p>	The tasting menus can be catered to your preference &#8211; three-, four- and five-course selections are offered at set prices during lunch and dinner.</p>
<p>	Sunday Brunch at Lacroix &#8211; which features such delectable dishes as baby lamb chops with garlic crust and banyuls sauce, niman ranch smoked bacon, quail eggs with artichoke, golden beet and shiitakes, and french baguette toast with apple, raspberry and rosemary jam &#8211; is also highly recommended.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/the-rittenhouse/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Best Western Center City Hotel</title>
		<link>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/best-western-center-city-hotel/</link>
					<comments>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/best-western-center-city-hotel/#reviews</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 06:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/best-western-center-city-hotel/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Alexander Inn is one of Philadelphia&#180;s most popular and reasonably priced small hotels. Conveniently located in the heart of the Washington Square West neighborhood in Center City Philadelphia, the Alexander Inn is a great place to base your stay in Philadelphia. The décor of the hotel&#180;s 48 designer rooms is inspired by the style<a class="moretag" href="https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/best-western-center-city-hotel/"> Read more...</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>	The Alexander Inn is one of Philadelphia&acute;s most popular and reasonably priced small hotels.</p>
<p>	Conveniently located in the heart of the Washington Square West neighborhood in Center City Philadelphia, the Alexander Inn is a great place to base your stay in Philadelphia.</p>
<p>	The décor of the hotel&acute;s 48 designer rooms is inspired by the style of the grand cruise ships of the 1930s, which is reflected in the rooms’ hand selected furnishings, fabrics and accessories. Beautiful artwork adorns the walls of each rooms, which all include private baths with plush towels.</p>
<p>	Rooms are also fitted with DirecTV (including many complimentary channels like CNN, ESPN, eight movie channels, etc.) and telephones with modem ports and direct dial. You will also have access to the hotel&acute;s free 24-hour fitness and e-mail centers.  </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/best-western-center-city-hotel/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Four Seasons Philadelphia</title>
		<link>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/four-seasons-philadelphia/</link>
					<comments>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/four-seasons-philadelphia/#reviews</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 06:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/four-seasons-philadelphia/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Overview The Philadelphia Downtown Courtyard opened it&#180;s doors after a grand $75 million restoration, recapturing the grandeur of its 1926 origins while incorporating state of the art systems throughout. Designed by renowned architect Phillip H. Johnson, the 18-story, 498-room hotel is listed on the “National Register of Historic Places” and stands as a charming testament<a class="moretag" href="https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/four-seasons-philadelphia/"> Read more...</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3>Overview </h3>
<p>	The Philadelphia Downtown Courtyard opened it&acute;s doors after a grand $75 million restoration, recapturing the grandeur of its 1926 origins while incorporating state of the art systems throughout.</p>
<p>	Designed by renowned architect Phillip H. Johnson, the 18-story, 498-room hotel is listed on the “National Register of Historic Places” and stands as a charming testament to time with elegant bronze work, plaster detailing, striking marble finishes and unique architectural details.</p>
<p>	Catering to both leisure and business travelers, the historic full-service hotel is ideally located in the “Heart of Center City” across from City Hall, one block to the Pennsylvania Convention Center and within walking distance of the Financial &#038; Historic Districts, Avenue of the Arts and some of the finest restaurants and shopping the city has to offer.</p>
<h3>Guestroom Features </h3>
<p>	The hotel features stylishly appointed oversized guestrooms with 11ft-high ceilings, a 42” LCD TV, Refrigerator, I-Pod Docking Station Alarm Clock, complimentary Wireless or Wired internet access, and Marriott&acute;s plush Revive bedding package.</p>
<p>	In addition, the property offers 61 suites for those who like additional room and added comfort as well as 50 rooms which include a striking Wall Mural of Philadelphia&acute;s Independence Hall.</p>
<h3>Hotel Services </h3>
<p>	As the largest Courtyard by Marriott in the United States, this hotel is truly unique offering all the full-service features and amenities you would expect from a premier hotel.</p>
<p>	The Annex Grille &#038; Lounge serves American Cuisine for breakfast, lunch &#038; dinner as well as is a great location for a refreshing beverage or cocktail. Or you can dine in the convenience of your guestroom with the hotel&acute;s evening Room Service.</p>
<p>	The hotel&acute;s Lobby Concierge Services and Bellman are ready to assist you with any request as well as information on all Philadelphia has to offer.</p>
<p>	Stay in shape in the hotel&acute;s State of the Art Fitness Center, and then unwind in the Indoor Pool and Whirlpool. If you are looking for a quiet place to getaway, visit our Philip H. Johnson Library where you can read all about Historic Philadelphia.</p>
<h3>Meetings &#038; Events </h3>
<p>	Recently featured on WE TV&acute;s “My Fair Wedding”, the Courtyard Marriott Philadelphia is one of the city&acute;s leading venues for corporate and social affairs with over 10,000 sq ft of flexible meeting space, including two Grand Ballrooms each with over 3,000 square feet accommodating up to 250 people. In addition, the hotel has a total of 11 meeting rooms making it an ideal home for all occasions. The hotel boasts an experienced full-service Event and Culinary Teams, ready to take care of all the details and ensure your event is not only a success, but a lasting memory. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/four-seasons-philadelphia/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Courtyard Philadelphia Downtown</title>
		<link>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/courtyard-philadelphia-downtown/</link>
					<comments>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/courtyard-philadelphia-downtown/#reviews</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 06:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/courtyard-philadelphia-downtown/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Overview The Philadelphia Downtown Courtyard opened it&#180;s doors after a grand $75 million restoration, recapturing the grandeur of its 1926 origins while incorporating state of the art systems throughout. Designed by renowned architect Phillip H. Johnson, the 18-story, 498-room hotel is listed on the “National Register of Historic Places” and stands as a charming testament<a class="moretag" href="https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/courtyard-philadelphia-downtown/"> Read more...</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3>Overview </h3>
<p>	The Philadelphia Downtown Courtyard opened it&acute;s doors after a grand $75 million restoration, recapturing the grandeur of its 1926 origins while incorporating state of the art systems throughout.</p>
<p>	Designed by renowned architect Phillip H. Johnson, the 18-story, 498-room hotel is listed on the “National Register of Historic Places” and stands as a charming testament to time with elegant bronze work, plaster detailing, striking marble finishes and unique architectural details.</p>
<p>	Catering to both leisure and business travelers, the historic full-service hotel is ideally located in the “Heart of Center City” across from City Hall, one block to the Pennsylvania Convention Center and within walking distance of the Financial &#038; Historic Districts, Avenue of the Arts and some of the finest restaurants and shopping the city has to offer.</p>
<h3>Guestroom Features </h3>
<p>	The hotel features stylishly appointed oversized guestrooms with 11ft-high ceilings, a 42” LCD TV, Refrigerator, I-Pod Docking Station Alarm Clock, complimentary Wireless or Wired internet access, and Marriott&acute;s plush Revive bedding package.</p>
<p>	In addition, the property offers 61 suites for those who like additional room and added comfort as well as 50 rooms which include a striking Wall Mural of Philadelphia&acute;s Independence Hall.</p>
<h3>Hotel Services </h3>
<p>	As the largest Courtyard by Marriott in the United States, this hotel is truly unique offering all the full-service features and amenities you would expect from a premier hotel.</p>
<p>	The Annex Grille &#038; Lounge serves American Cuisine for breakfast, lunch &#038; dinner as well as is a great location for a refreshing beverage or cocktail. Or you can dine in the convenience of your guestroom with the hotel&acute;s evening Room Service.</p>
<p>	The hotel&acute;s Lobby Concierge Services and Bellman are ready to assist you with any request as well as information on all Philadelphia has to offer.</p>
<p>	Stay in shape in the hotel&acute;s State of the Art Fitness Center, and then unwind in the Indoor Pool and Whirlpool. If you are looking for a quiet place to getaway, visit our Philip H. Johnson Library where you can read all about Historic Philadelphia.</p>
<h3>Meetings &#038; Events </h3>
<p>	Recently featured on WE TV&acute;s “My Fair Wedding”, the Courtyard Marriott Philadelphia is one of the city&acute;s leading venues for corporate and social affairs with over 10,000 sq ft of flexible meeting space, including two Grand Ballrooms each with over 3,000 square feet accommodating up to 250 people. In addition, the hotel has a total of 11 meeting rooms making it an ideal home for all occasions. The hotel boasts an experienced full-service Event and Culinary Teams, ready to take care of all the details and ensure your event is not only a success, but a lasting memory. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/courtyard-philadelphia-downtown/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hilton Inn at Penn</title>
		<link>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/hilton-inn-at-penn/</link>
					<comments>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/hilton-inn-at-penn/#reviews</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 06:13:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/hilton-inn-at-penn/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Located in the heart of Penn&#180;s campus in the beautiful University City neighborhood of Philadelphia, The Hilton Inn at Penn is a great choice for accommodations during your upcoming visit to Philadelphia. The location puts you right in the middle of the prestigious University of Pennsylvania and its many nearby educational, medical and corporate centers.<a class="moretag" href="https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/hilton-inn-at-penn/"> Read more...</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>	Located in the heart of Penn&acute;s campus in the beautiful University City neighborhood of Philadelphia, The Hilton Inn at Penn is a great choice for accommodations during your upcoming visit to Philadelphia.</p>
<p>	The location puts you right in the middle of the prestigious University of Pennsylvania and its many nearby educational, medical and corporate centers. And Center City Philadelphia is only a short cab ride away. So if you want to get out and explore the city, you are set.</p>
<p>	Take in a show at the Annenberg Theater; visit one of the many museums the city has to offer; dine at area restaurants that boast a range of cuisines, from Thai to Indian to Japanese to classic comfort cuisine; peerless boutique shopping along Walnut Street from University City to Old City.</p>
<p>	The beautifully appointed guest rooms are equipped for the technologically sophisticated and include two dual-line phones with voice mail, data ports and high speed and wireless Internet access. Each room also offers WEBTV, plush terry cloth robes and luxurious bath amenities provide a touch of indulgence. Additionally, a refreshment center is now located in each guestroom with snacks and refreshments along with an in room safe for valuables and laptops.</p>
<p>	The Hilton Inn at Penn is a recipient of the AAA Four Diamond rating. There is also a 24-hour fitness center with a full range of cardiovascular and weight training equipment.</p>
<h3>Penne Restaurant and Wine Bar </h3>
<p>	One of University City&acute;s finest Italian restaurants is Penne at the Inn at Penn. Featuring innovative, regional Italian cuisine and hand-made pasta made fresh daily, Penne is a great choice for lunch or dinner.</p>
<p>	The pasta is handmade right in front of you and then dished up along side delectable entrées such as grilled veal tenderloin and honey glazed sea scallops. And the wine bar offers more than 30 varieties by the glass and more than 100 by the bottle.  </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://pintyaking.github.io/Smartcity/places/hilton-inn-at-penn/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
